<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Guide for Beyblade</string>
    <string name="app_name_for_title" translatable="false">Guide for Beyblade Burst 2k20</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="book1title">About game</string>
    <string name="book1body">Beyblade Burst Mobile is a Beyblade Burst game published by Hasbro. It is available on Android and iOS. The game allows you to scan QR codes included with Hasbro Beyblade products. The player can then customize their Beyblade using the parts they\'ve unlocked.</string>
    <string name="book_1_title">Gameplay</string>
    <string name="book_1_body">Overall, even for a beginner, the gameplay is simple. The game initially has 5 Beyblades unlocked for the player to choose from: Valtryek Wing Accel, Spryzen Spread Fusion, Roktavor Heavy Survive, Kerbeus Central Defense (Hasbro), and Z Achilles 11 Xtend. The player can customize any of their Beyblades by selecting the Edit option in the Beylocker, then selecting the Forge Disc and Performance Tip to equip to the Energy Layer. Players can also choose which color they want to use for each part, though they must be unlocked first. New parts and part color variants can be unlocked either by scanning the QR code on the physical product or can be purchased from the in-game Store. Parts, Beystadiums, and new Beyblades can be purchased with in-game currency called Beycoins earned from gameplay. The game does not have any option to use real-world money. New items are cycled into the shop 7 days after first visiting. The timer does not start counting down again until the player visits again.
        \n
        \n

        In addition to battling, in-game currency and experience points can be earned by using Battle Track. The game will automatically run multiple matches between the selected Beyblade and randomly generated opponents over a 4 hour period. Once completed, the player can claim their reward with Beycoins, experience points, and Beypoints which act as player experience. Individual parts all gain the same experience from a given match and can be leveled up, improving their statistics. When the player levels up, it unlocks new character icons, Beystadiums, and game-exclusive skins for parts. The player can level up to 99, while Beyblade parts can each level up to 5. Despite having a low maximum level, the difference between one level and the next is significant. Beating a Beyblade of a higher level gives an Underdog bonus, which scales based on the difference in level. Winning without drawing or losing will also give a bonus, and finish a match with a Burst Finish will award extra Beycoins.
        \n
        \n
        Like the real game, Beyblades are divided into four types - Attack, Defense, Stamina, and Balance. The type advantages of the toys are present in the game as well, though more emphasized by advantaged Beyblades doing more Stamina and Burst Meter damage to their opponents. A match starts with the player lining up their launch, then tapping the screen in time with the countdown timer. With each tap, the range gets narrower. The player can get a "Perfect Launch" by tapping correctly enough times to fill the energy meter above the time, 8 out of the 10 available times to do so. A Perfect Launch gives the player extra stamina beyond the normal maximum at launch. Once launched, both Beyblades will move around the Beystadium on their own, occasionally moving in to attack. A round ends when one or both players have their Stamina or Burst Meter depleted. One point is awarded for Survivor Finishes and two for Burst Finishes. Unlike the physical game, Draws have points awarded to both players as appropriate for the finish type. Of example, if one player spins out and the other bursts, one player will get one point while the other gets two.
        \n
        \n
        The player has two meters that steadily fill throughout the fight - the Basic Ability and the Avatar Attack. These can also be filled quicker by collecting Ability and Avatar Orbs by tapplin on them. Once a meter is filled, the player can activate that ability. For Basic Abilities, Attack Types will perform a Smash Attack, Defense Types will take the center and force the opponent to attack, Stamina Types will recharge their Stamina Meter (but not Burst Meter), and Balance Types will have a random Basic Ability which changes each time it\'s used. However, all of these can be countered; the Smash Attack can be reversed if the opponent is Defense Type and activates its ability first, the forced attack of a Defense Type taking the center can be escaped by a Stamina type activating its recharge (or if the ability was poorly timed, any opponent my move away rather than attacking), and a Stamina Type\'s recharge will stop if it takes damage in any way. The Avatar Attack will instead bring up a quick time event where the player must tap at the right time, with different meters for different Beyblades. Depending on the player\'s timing, an Avatar Attack will do a large amount of damage (from 50% to 100% of a predetermined value) which also lowers the opponent\'s Burst Meter faster than normal clashes or Basic Abilities.
        \n
        \n
        The game features an achievement system that rewards the player with Beypoints for completing specific goals. These can be anything from scanning a certain type of product to winning a number of battles to collecting a number of orbs during matches. A weekly challenge, changed every Sunday at midnight, will have a more specific goal such as defeating a specific type of Beyblade with another type. The player can also watch instructional videos or promotional clips from the anime.
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_2_title">Game Modes</string>
    <string name="book_2_body">Battle League:
        \n
    • My Leagues: \n Allows the player to create a League. They can select a time frame and which of their friends are invited. This can be used for tournaments or single matches.
   \n
    • World Events: \n Various types of tournaments the player can join. Each has an entry fee. Players are ranked based on points, with the winner having the most at the end.
\nSingle Elimination: \n The player is knocked out of the rankings if they lose a single match.
\n Triple Elimination: \n The player is knocked out of the rankings after three losses in a bracket.
\n 10 Match Tournament:\n The player participates in 10 matches.
\n Toy Battles:\n
    • Head to Head: \n A single match battle. \n
    • Tournament:\n The player can set up a one-time tournament bracket with players on their friend list.\n
Quick Battle: \n
    • Battle A Friend: Allows players to face off against one another. The other player must be on your friends list.\n
    • Random Opponent: A random player who is also looking for an opponent is selected.\n
    • Exhibition Battle: The player faces off against a CPU-controlled player.\n
Custom Opponent:\n The player selects the parts and levels for their opponent Beyblade.\n
Random Opponent:\n The game randomly assembles a Beyblade to fight. However, it can and will often create opponents much stronger than the player if they do not use a Beyblade with all level 5 parts.
        \n
Training: The player selects a Beyblade of the appropriate type. The game teaches the advantages of that type and the abilities it has.
\n
        Challenges:\n The player battles a series of predetermined Beyblades. The player must pay an entry fee to begin a challenge, but will earn money and experience for each victory. Depending on how far they get into the challenge, the player can also win a bonus for first, second, or third place. Challenges can have requirement such as a specific Beyblade, type, or level.
        \n
        \n

    </string>
    <string name="book_3_title">Trivia</string>
    <string name="book_3_body">
       The icon for the game is Valtryek V2, using the Epic Rivals Battle Set coloration. \n\n
There are custom avatars in the game which are similar to the characters in the anime. ( Valt, Shu, Wakia, Daigo, Red Eye, etc.) However, none of them are completely accurate in appearance to the characters themselves.\n\n
The game allows a wide variety of customization, including customizing CPU controlled opponents. However, it has some limitations:\n\n
SwitchStrike parts with mode change gimmicks, such as Energy Layer - Spryzen Requiem S3\'s spin direction or the selectable tips on Performance Tip - Trans, can be selected before rounds in a match; this will adjust their statistics accordingly. However, others such as Energy Layer - Wyvron W3 or Performance Tip - Nothing where the feature is automatic or otherwise not in the player\'s control will instead have one or two extra Basic Abilities which can be activated once each per round but don\'t recharge from collecting Energy Orbs. This is likely due to such gimmicks not being easily visualized in the game\'s simplistic mechanics.\n\n
Forge Discs with Disc Frames are treated as a single item, with each combination of Disc and Frame being given its own part code. For example, Forge Disc - 4 with Disc Frame - Meteor is given the code D65, while 4 on its own is D50.\n\n
Slingshock tips cannot change mode, and therefore cannot take more aggressive movement patterns.\n
GT Chips cannot be switched between Layer Bases on HyperSphere Energy Layers.\n\n
All Beystadiums of a given type - Basic, Slingshock, or HyperSphere - will have identical performance to all others of the same type. Beystadiums with gimmicks that affect performance, such as being larger or having multiple levels\n\n
The statistics assigned to parts in-game does not always reflect their real world performance.\n\n
Some appear to be based on the theoretical abilities the toys are intended to have, such as Energy Layer - Balkesh B3 having high Defense based on its gap-blocking gimmick.\n\n
Rip Fire parts in-game have higher Attack, Defense, or Weight statistics compared to their standard counterparts. However, in real life, they are not competitively viable due to the higher Burst rates (including self-Burst) and lower weight of Rip Fire Forge Discs compared to the normal versions.\n\n
Dual Layers released under new names for Turbo, such as Energy Layer - Anubion A2 recolored as Energy Layer - Lava-X Anubion A4, have different in-game statistics despite being the exact same mold and performing near identically to their original versions.\n\n
Beyblades in-game will never lose stamina over time from friction, only from clashing with each other. Stamina type Beyblades have the ability to replenish their Stamina with their Basic Ability, but not their Burst Meter.\n\n
The game doesn\'t allow the player to type any username they wish. Instead, two words are selected from separate predetermined lists with a sequential number added at the end. When creating a new profile, the user does not directly select the words but taps a button which randomly selects each part, which can be repeated until receiving the desired words.\n\n
Due to the limited number of possible QR codes and the codes themselves lacking registers (marks that determine orientation for QR codes), some codes will unlock multiple items in-game. This is due to the QR codes basically being identical but rotated 90 or 180 degrees relative to each other. For example, Dullahan D5 11 Linear-H uses the same code as the Battle Tower Beystadium. Scanning the code twice will unlock both.\n\n
When the game was first updated to include Slingshock Beyblades, recolored Dual Layers released with new names were treated as color variations of the original. For example, Energy Layer - Blizzard-X Gaianon G4 was treated as a variation of Energy Layer - Gaianon G2. However, a later update separated them, with customized parts being applied to the original while the new version would be given its default parts. This also reverted the Slingshock Energy Layer to level 1, even if the Forge Disc and Performance Tip it was included with had been leveled up since.\n\n
The game originally only allowed Beyblades that had been physically scanned to activate Battle Track, which was originally called Avatar Track. Beyblades which had been purchased from the store could still be scanned to allow Avatar Track to be used. A later update changed this so that all Beyblades that the player unlocked could use Battle Track, and changed the name.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="book_4_title">About Rage-Quitting – Save It For Career Mode, And Only When Needed</string>
    <string name="book_4_body">
        Now this is something where we always tread lightly when discussing. Rage-quitting, as any gamer should know, is a practice that is typically discouraged, mainly because it invalidates the human opponent’s hard work, allowing the rage-quitter to start out fresh without actually taking a loss. But with that out of the way, we would only recommend rage-quitting in Dream League Soccer 2020 modes that do not involve human-controlled clubs. That means you’re free to do this in Career Mode, but certainly not if you’re in multiplayer action, lest you face getting banned from online play.
        \n
        \n
        When rage-quitting during a match, there’s a method to the madness, so to say — you need to exit the app while the ball is live in order to restart from the last dead ball. If you quit a match after your opponent has scored a goal, their goal will still count, though you can definitely quit the app after a missed penalty and try making the shot again. (Likewise, you can also rage-quit successfully after scoring a goal, effectively saving your progress after the last really good thing you did.)
        \n
        \n
        What happens, however, if you’re deep in a hole without previously quitting the app and restarting it, and want to go back several minutes into the match in order to have another go at it? Sadly, you can only restart from the last dead ball, and if you quit the match (as opposed to the app), that’s going to count as a forfeit on your end — an automatic loss with no currency rewards whatsoever.
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_5_title">Earn More Gems By Achieving Your Club’s Goals
</string>
    <string name="book_5_body">
        We’ve already talked about how you can earn coins for completing a match in Career Mode, but what about gems, which are the game’s premium currency? As the game mentions after you’ve played a couple matches, you can earn gems by completing the achievements listed in the Statistics section under My Club — yes, we know it’s a rather strange name for what is normally called just plain “Achievements” or “Goals,” but these club goals are related to team statistics, so we kind of understand why First Touch went with this term.
        \n
        \n
        As you’ll see in the Statistics section, your first four club goals will earn you 10 Gems each — you will first need to finish 8th or higher in the Academy Division, reach Round 2 of the Global Challenge Cup, win at least four games in the Academy Division, and score at least 15 goals (i.e. one goal per match on average) in the Academy Division. These are generally easy goals to achieve, though you can certainly expect them to get more difficult as your club gets better and you progress from one division/league to the next. More achievements accomplished means more Gems, so make sure to review the Statistics menu to know what you need to aim for!
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_6_title">Help Your Players Reach Their Potential By Hiring Coaches
</string>
    <string name="book_6_body">
        Whether you’re in between matches or preparing for the actual match itself, Dream League Soccer 2020 allows you to train your players by hiring Coaches, effectively giving them permanent statistical boosts and helping them edge closer toward their potential. There are three types of Coaches you can hire — Technical (improves Ball Control, Distribution, Shooting, and Tackling), Fitness (Strength, Stamina, Speed, and Acceleration), and Goalkeeping (Shot Stopping and Handling) — and your first Common hire for each category is on the house.
        \n
        \n
        Subsequent hires, however, will cost you some Gems — a Common Coach trains one player, improves one random stat, and provides a +2 stat increase for 15 Gems, a Rare one trains two players for one random stat and a +3 increase for 40 Gems, and a Legendary one trains three players for all applicable stats and a +5 increase for the hefty price of 150 Gems.
        \n
        \n
        Although it would be nice to be able to choose a specific player to train — ideally, you want to focus on your better players and not the weaker ones who would likely be relegated to the bench more often than not — the main caveat with this feature is the fact that the game chooses a random player to be impacted by the Coach’s training.
        \n
        \n
        As we’ve observed, it’s the scrubs that usually get trained before the better ones, and while that makes sense (in the real world, you want to help a less skilled player improve, rather than someone who’s already quite skilled), this may not be the most ideal of situations. Still, every bit of improvement counts if you’re trying to improve your team as you go along, so make use of those coaching hires if you can afford them, but don’t overuse this feature!
        \n
        \n
        In addition, since you can only have so many players on your club until you upgrade your stadium, you can also release your weaker players in exchange for a Technical or Fitness Coach (for non-goalkeepers) or a Goalkeeping Coach (for goalkeepers). In effect, you’re sacrificing your weaker players for a chance to improve your stronger ones, so that’s always something you can look into if you’re trying to save on resources. This feature can be found in the Transfers menu (on the bottom right, below Agent), and that’s the very next topic we shall be discussing in this guide, so keep reading!
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_7_title">The Transfer Market – Buy New Players With Coins To Improve Your Roster
</string>
    <string name="book_7_body">
        On the lower left part of the main menu, below Next Fixture, you’ll see the Transfers menu, and this is where you can manually add new players to your club and actually choose the players you want to add, instead of randomly drafting them with a Scout or an Agent, though those two options are available in the Transfer screen as well. So what’s in it for you if you’re trying to improve your club through through this feature?
        \n
        \n
        Just to set your expectations, the players that are available on the Live Transfers list will typically be almost in line with those on your club in terms of their overall rating. That means you can certainly expect common players rated 67 or lower if you’re in the Academy Division and just starting out. However, the good thing about this is that you don’t need to spend any Gems — just a few hundred coins for the common players, and as we said earlier, a lot of them will typically be slightly better than your team average. Again, not that much better, but that is, at least, better than nothing, right?
        \n
        \n
        As for the other options available in Transfer, you can use a Scout to make two players available — you have a Common, Rare, and Legendary option, with the odds of getting Rare and Legendary players increasing as you move along, and same with the price in coins to use this Scout. (To be specific, that’s 75 for a Common scout, 240 for Rare, and 500 for Legendary.) To clarify, you still could get Common rarity players even if you use a Legendary scout, as the odds of getting Common, Rare, and Legendary players through this option are as follows — 40 percent, 45 percent, and 15 percent.
        \n
        \n
        In addition, we should also let you know that the aforementioned costs are onetime fees for your Scout, and are separate from the amount of coins you’ll need to pay to actually buy the players, who will be available in the Scout section only until your next match is completed. Lastly, the position of the players you can get through this option will always be randomized — it wouldn’t matter if you’re already loaded at a given position!
        \n
        \n
        As for the Agent option, the main difference here is that you are actually guaranteed one player (just one, this time around) of the rarity in question — Common for 30 Gems, Rare for 150, and Legendary for 300. The position will still be completely random, so there’s still going to be a fair bit of gambling involved here. Still, it’s something you may want to save up for as you complete more achievements and earn more Gems over time.
        \n
        \n
        That would be all for now as far as our Dream League Soccer 2020 beginner’s guide is concerned. Stay tuned as we may come back with another guide for the game with some advanced tips and tricks!
        \n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="some_long_text" translatable="false">Overall, even for a beginner, the gameplay is simple. The game initially has 5 Beyblades unlocked for the player to choose from: Valtryek Wing Accel, Spryzen Spread Fusion, Roktavor Heavy Survive, Kerbeus Central Defense (Hasbro), and Z Achilles 11 Xtend. The player can customize any of their Beyblades by selecting the Edit option in the Beylocker, then selecting the Forge Disc and Performance Tip to equip to the Energy Layer. Players can also choose which color they want to use for each part, though they must be unlocked first. New parts and part color variants can be unlocked either by scanning the QR code on the physical product or can be purchased from the in-game Store. Parts, Beystadiums, and new Beyblades can be purchased with in-game currency called Beycoins earned from gameplay. The game does not have any option to use real-world money. New items are cycled into the shop 7 days after first visiting. The timer does not start counting down again until the player visits again.</string>


    <string name="hello_world">hello world</string>

</resources>